<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">CS188Project3</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_midwest_philosophy">MidwestPhilosophy</string>
    <string name="title_activity_states">States</string>
    <string name="title_activity_iowa">Iowa</string>
    <string name="title_activity_appetizers2">Appetizers2</string>
    <string name="title_activity_grilled_corn">GrilledCorn</string>
    <string name="title_activity_holidays">Holidays</string>
    <string name="title_activity_potluck">Potluck</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bbc">BBC</string>
    <string name="midwest_philosophy">Midwest nice. We’re proud of it. You know, like that two-finger wave people exchange when they drive by, well, everyone. And what better way to share that flyover-state love than by turning a friend’s refrigerator (or your own) into a mosaic of casserole/hotdish delicacies — yeah, we’ll keep brainstorming bacon T-shirt ideas to avoid that argument. 

Whether you’re craving the artery-clogging comfort of deep-fried everything or are flabbergasted by your (now-former) friend’s unfamiliarity with the “walking taco,” Mmmidwest takes you on a culinary journey through the finest in “just-add-soup” cuisine, beer, cheese and obviously, more bacon.
	
We’re all about comfort food in the Midwest and really, what’s more comforting than family members convincing you to eat that second helping of tater-tot casserole? 

Forget those practically microscopic dishes plated on square, immaculate dinnerware. Trade plates for your very own bag of Doritos, per the walking taco. Eat everything on a stick and remember, with perseverance, you can deep-fry anything. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_illinois">Illinois</string>
    <string name="title_activity_minnesota">Minnesota</string>
    <string name="title_activity_wisconsin">Wisconsin</string>
    <string name="title_activity_recipe_page">RecipePage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_favorites">UserFavorites</string>
    <string name="title_activity_favorite">Favorite</string>

</resources>
